未来
新しい空
キラメキが
真歌しいね
今が日はみんなで
君はしょう
It's a picnic, but I can't forget the dream of a man
Of course, I'll always be with you
I'll be with you forever, I'll always be with you
I'll always be with you
I'll always be with you forever, I'll always be with you
You and you, you and you
If I love you forever, I'll always be with you
I hope for the memories you get from me
Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh, Woh...
If our life for the most person lives another real life, we'll soon come back and become rich someday.
We've been ruined in the rest of world by being rich!
We'll also know where the world or where we'll go and go back to the world if we're rich and whatever we can!
But, we didn't find a way to do so that's what we should've been.
It was a big show with the addition of autumn school and the children of adults.
I was looking forward to this world together with Muka!
Muka Muka with Kimo Damage!
That's right!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Really, if you jump from here, you'll get a headache!
Yeah!
I'm sick, Muka Muka!
Wow, I'm so scared!
Do you really like it?
No, I don't want to get a headache.
I want to get a headache!
I don't want to get a headache.
Don't forget to get a headache like that.
It's a good idea, isn't it?
Really, really.
Oh, you guys.
You can't just eat it.
You haven't?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
My courage comes from here!
We all have a馬尺!
I'm the only one who can make it, Okinawa!
You are the only one who can make it!
Oh, I got a headache!
You know what, Raka-san?
What did you say about me?
On the next day, my friend.
Then, the next time.
Oh, you guys were all friends!
Huh? It's a joke!
What are you doing?
You're doing this to get out of here!
I'm sorry.
Hey!
I was just kidding.
You're a joke, so it's a joke.
You're doing this to get out of here?
That...
Is it because the car that's on fire is on fire?
That's what you're doing?
Yeah!
You're a coward!
You're a woman!
What?
He's not doing it!
I can't do it! I'm going to try my best!
Well, I'm not going to do it. I'm not going to do it.
Uiba, hurry up and do it. I want to do it one more time.
I want to do it one more time. I want to do it one more time.
What are you doing? Are you going to put on your clothes?
I'm going to put on my clothes.
Let's go!
I'm going to put on my clothes. I'm going to put on my clothes.
You got the face out of it?
YouMUSIC, Ten cappuccino.
So I don't do this.
Go!
She didn't touch me.
Don't touch me I meant it.
Quickly!
I'm going to do it!
Hmm...
Well then, let's make some food.
This is the first time I've ever seen a food like this.
It's fun to eat.
It's like a child.
Well, that's Yoh-chan's charm, but...
Hey, this...
I don't think this is the right way to do this.
Well, you're so lucky!
Well, it's great. It's just a piece of cake, Meme-shiya.
It looks delicious if you look at it.
No way!
I don't think it's good to eat it, either.
Yoh-chan, it's just a piece of cake.
It's just a piece of cake. I can't eat it anymore.
It's not a piece of cake. It's important to find a piece of cake in the forest.
Huh? It's just a piece of cake, Yoh-chan.
It's a piece of cake, Yoh-chan.
You can't say anything if you think so.
Well, that's a piece of cake.
Wow! You're so happy with your parents again!
You're not happy with your parents.
You're making a meal.
If you're done, you'll surely be the owner of Takagaya's shop, the owner of Takagaya's shop.
Wow! It's amazing!
You can make a meal by yourself.
Huh?
I'll do my best to make a wonderful meal for you.
How is it, Yoh-chan?
Shall we go to the shop?
How is it?
Let's do it!
Yoh-chan!
Shall we go to the shop?
Shop, shop!
Don't worry about it.
I'll make a meal for you, too.
Mom, you have to be careful there.
Wait, where are you going?
It's hot even if it's raining.
Even if it's raining, it's fine.
Yoh-chan!
It's amazing that the summer sun is coming out today.
I wonder if it's going to take some time.
Yeah.
No, no, no, it's going to take some time.
Oh, I got it.
Hey!
Wait!
What are you doing, Dad?
What?
I'm going to...
Hey!
It's hot, right?
No, it's not.
It's not like that.
It's not like you're going to get wet.
What's going to happen in this school?
You're going to get wet even if it's raining, right?
It's not like that.
Huh?
You're going to get wet too?
It's not like that.
What did you get?
You're going to get wet even if it's raining.
It's not like you're going to get wet.
What?
Why are you doing this?
I see.
It's the best result of the H-Get.
It's not like that.
I'm going to get wet.
I'm going to get wet too.
I'm going to get wet because my mom is kind.
That's right.
If it's like this, it's not like that.
Huh?
Oh...
It's a curry flower.
It's called a butterfly flower.
It's not like this.
I'm going to get wet!
Oh!
What's going on, Muka?
Do you want to get wet?
I'm going to get wet!
Alright, that's it for today.
Let's get wet.
What's going on?
Don't let me get wet.
Are you going to get wet?
If you get wet, you can get wet by yourself.
Huh?
What's wrong?
You're doing it on purpose.
No!
You're not going to get wet.
You're going to get wet by yourself.
Father, you're going to get wet by yourself.
Why are you doing this again?
You're going to get wet by me.
I'm going to get wet by myself.
I've changed my mind because I've changed my mind.
I don't think I want to change.
You're saying that, right?
It's not enough to get wet by yourself.
I said that.
I'm going to get wet by myself.
What?
It's my female partner.
I can't do it in my own way.
What's wrong, Father?
It's not a joke.
I don't know at all.
It's sad.
You don't need to worry about me.
We're going to get wet by ourselves.
I'm going to get wet by myself.
I'm going to get wet.
That's Tamaranguji.
I want to get wet.
What?
I'm going to get wet by myself.
I want to get wet by myself.
We're going to get wet by ourselves.
That's a bit too much.
What do you think?
You're going to get wet by yourself.
Let's go.
What?
I'm going to get wet.
You're not going to get wet by yourself.
I'm going to get wet by myself.
I don't want to go to a place like this.
You're not going to get wet by yourself.
That's a good plan.
It's not a good plan.
It's a joke.
It's the final result of the victory.
If it's a victory, we'll have to do it tomorrow, right?
Eh?
What's the point of the victory?
I'll tell you in the end.
Even if you say so, it's because we're the only men in front of Nika Nika.
The men in front of Nika?
What are you saying?
You're wearing a tachyon shirt, so you're wearing a tachyon shirt, aren't you?
You're wearing a tachyon shirt, aren't you?
Hey!
I'm not wearing a tachyon shirt.
Do you think Nika Nika was a man?
That's right.
You're wearing a tachyon shirt, aren't you?
What?
Uiba.
What do you mean by that?
I don't know.
Huh?
Hey!
If it's a man, we'll play together.
Yay, Nika Nika!
Working at men?
Not believe it!
There's always one way in this neighborhood!
Let regarder Nika Nika in the Elytra.
Nika Nika is a new fellow in Tokori Dakakin who won the Kyoryuichi couple.
Rogu made6 from five people and also put an order from this kind of buns around the neck,
so the Japanese people wouldn't be able to find it.
It is not easy to say things like that!
Inside buns?
Aah!
That's right.
It's more delicious when you always throw it around the neck!
Yay!
That's right. I love you so much.
Oh, wait!
Wait a minute! Where are you going?
Oh, it's not time for you to take off.
Don't laugh at me.
You're so weird these days.
I want to see you drink something.
It's not like that. I'm just kidding.
Oh, wait!
What do you mean?
I always try to be a fool.
Yeah, I'm a fool.
I'll never let you lose such a vision!
Well, then, it's a good thing you've been doing since you were 5,000 years old.
It's a good thing you've been doing. You're not being rude.
That's right.
You've been doing a good thing since you were 5,000 years old.
I can't eat this.
This is the order, Mr. Koji.
Wait!
I'll explain it to you if you're going to die.
Yes.
The food is the most difficult place to eat in the Kyoji River.
If you eat this, you'll be able to eat it.
Good job, Koji.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Stop.
I can't do anything if I'm angry.
What?
That's a power.
It's not like I can't find a mom.
Mom!
Is there such a thing?
It's a lie.
What's wrong, Rukun?
Are you scared?
Stop it, baby.
What are you going to do?
Are you scared that you're going to die?
Are you scared?
What?
It's delicious, Rukun.
And the most important thing is that
you're going to be surprised by a girl's coldness.
And you're going to be surprised by a girl's coldness.
Are you scared?
It's a lie.
I'm scared.
Why?
Are you scared?
I'm scared.
What are you doing?
I told you to do this.
What?
Are you scared?
I've been using it for a long time.
It's okay.
I'm still dreaming of a woman.
I want to go home early.
Muka, Muka!
We don't want to see each other again.
I don't know which way to go,
but I'll take care of you.
I'll take care of you.
Muka, Muka!
Where did you go?
I'll take care of Muka's honey for you.
I'll take care of you.
Let's go!
Huh?!
We're going to the lines!
What are we going to do?
Are we going to the station with the only three of us?
It's okay!
We're going to the station with the six of us.
Jontan!
I don't know why, but we're going to the station.
I don't think you should go there.
I'm not going to go to the station with these two of my friends.
The two of us went to the station,
and they went to the station together.
I'll be back in the first place!
I can't be like this!
I can't live without you!
It's so hot!
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to let you go!
The difference between a family is so good!
I think I should go home, isn't it?
Let's go to Tokyo with the love you've been able to get here.
Love?
It's called love, isn't it?
If it's a love, it's stronger than Tokyo.
That's right!
Oh, my God!
It looks so good!
There's a huge hole in this area.
There's a hole in the hole.
Maybe this sound is a hole in the hole?
What kind of hole is it?
Are we going to break the wall?
We haven't seen anything yet, do we?
There's a hole in the hole in the hole,
and there's a hole in the hole in the hole.
Now, there's a hole in the hole.
Let's go, go, go!
There's a hole in the hole,
I mean, I don't think it's going to be that good.
It's a hole in the hole.
Damn!
I threw the hole in the hole!
I don't know.
Maybe it's too close to the hole.
Let's go, go.
That's scary.
I was...
Where is it? It's Wibata.
Wibata!
Hatsuki!
We've been waiting for you for a while.
It's so strange! We've been attacked by Mamonu!
We've been attacked by Mamonu!
Wibata!
You've come!
What?
This is it!
Amazing, Kanzu!
The Mamonu was the first time we were attacked by a real man!
Let's go!
I love you, Tatsuki!
Let's go! Let's go!
Wibata!
Wibata! Hurry up!
Let's go!
Wibata!
What are you doing?
What?
I'm scared!
I told you!
Wibata!
Let's go!
Come back!
I don't know if you're hiding something!
Don't stop!
What are you doing?
I've finally come here!
Let's take all the water!
Let's go!
You're so good, Mom!
Really?
I didn't experience it for a while!
That's right!
I feel like I'm dreaming!
I love you!
How are you?
I know!
How do you like it?
I appreciate it!
You ate!
I brought it.
I'm here!
It's enough already
So?
Don't go!
You should change the lipstick!
We're all good boys!
We made a poor idea!
For how?
We're not really rich on during convention other than Chuu,
We don't get married,
Everyone's excited to go on a trip.
Let's go!
Let's do it!
Yes!
I'm done!
I'll get the special honey milk.
It's a good taste, right?
The sweet and sour taste.
You're done, Yoh-chan!
I'll take care of you.
I'm so curious.
I thought you were going to eat it.
Right?
It's my turn, right?
A chimise juice maruduzum!
It's a chimise juice maruduzum!
Let's eat it together!
It's delicious!
It's a delicious food maruduzum!
If you want to eat one, it's different!
Rain, rain, rain, rain, me..
Bell, dance,ʻ
Come on, come on, come on..
Look at it!
Guys are...
swimming so high!
Get ready to swim!
Let's swim later,
until there's a farm
The
way of the
time
is always
the voice
The voice
is here
Hey
Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang, bang